Guide to the Vice President for Student Affairs records, 1923-[ongoing] UA.09.02.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Vice President for Student Affairs records
1923-[ongoing]
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Office of Student Affairs.
UA.09.02.0002
103 Linear Feet
The Vice President of Student Affairs oversees the Division of Student Affairs, involved in all aspects of student life at Duke University. William J. Griffith was Dean of Student Affairs and then Vice President of Student Affairs from 1963-1991. The Vice President for Student Affairs Records include correspondence, reports, memorandums, and other materials related to the operations of the Division of Student Affairs and cover such topics as student organizations, student housing, student government, student activities, administrative planning around student facilities and resources, and many other subjects.
Collection Overview
The collection includes a wide variety of materials related to the operations of the Student Affairs office. Much of the collection is correspondence, with many reports, printed materials, and memorandums, as well as other materials.
Topics include student organizations and activities, including student government, fraternities, student living groups, interest groups, and publications; administrative activities and policies focused on student life and well-being, including student housing, student health and insurance, resources for supporting student life, and facilities for students; administrative and campus activities including arts and cultural activities such as the Duke Players, Chapel activities and services, and the Publications Board; and events of significance to the Duke community, including materials related to the Allen Building Takeover, protests and demonstrations, and many other topics.
An addition (Accession UA2018-0084) contains correpondence and subject files from Larry Moneta, VP of Student Affairs.
Some materials were removed April 2007 and now make up the Office of Student Affairs Reference Collection.
Historical Note
The Division of Student Affairs is led by the Vice President of Student Affairs. The office is involved in all aspects of student life at Duke University, providing programs and services "that support the optimal growth of Duke students, enhance their intellectual, social, cultural and physical development, and complement Duke's academic excellence by providing opportunities for students to experience education and explore interests beyond the classroom."
The first Dean of Student Affairs was Herbert Herring, who held the position in the 1950s. William Griffith became Dean of Student Affairs in 1963, later to be called the Vice President of Student Affairs, and served for almost thirty years before retiring in 1991. Under Griffith, the office developed the Student Union and Counseling and Psychological Services, and was deeply involved in shaping the Duke Publications Board, the Duke Players, the Duke Artists Series, the Associated Students of Duke University and its successor the Duke Student Government, and many student and student-focused organizations. Griffith was Dean of Student Affairs during the Duke Vigil in 1968 and the Allen Building Takeover in 1969, involved in the administrations response and follow-up to the latter. After retiring in 1991, the William J. Griffith University Service Award was named in his honor, and the Griffith Board Room in the Bryan Center was named for William and Carol Griffith.
Maureen Cullins was the Assistant to the Vice President of Student Affairs in the late 1980s and early 1990s. She is presently (2018) the Co-Director of the Multicultural Resource Center at the Duke University School of Medicine.
Larry Moneta was the Vice President for Student Affairs from 2001 to 2019.
Access Restrictions
Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
Conditions Governing Access
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Conditions Governing Access
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
Provenance
The Vice President for Student Affairs records were transferred between 1972 and 2018.
Conditions Governing Access
Records including the personal information of individual donors to the University will be closed for a period of 70 years.
Student housing -- North Carolina -- Durham; College students -- Housing; Duke University. Office of Student Affairs.; Griffith, William; Duke University. Undergraduate Publications Board; Associated Students of Duke University; Duke University. Duke Players; Duke University -- Students -- Societies, etc
- Accession A74-78, 1
  Scope and Contents
  This accession includes files from William Griffith's time as Vice President for Student Affairs. Alphabetized files include correspondence, reports, and other materials on the Duke Players and performance planning, the Duke University Union operations, student housing, student organizations, and other topics. Materials primarily date from the 1960s.
  - Academic Council: correspondence & general, 1964-1970 (Box 1)
  - Academic Freedom of Students, undated (Box 1)
  - Academic Standards, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Committee: proposal for graduate in Hospital Administration, circa 1961 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Council/Executive Committee of the Academic Council, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Admissions: correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 1)
  - Allied Arts: correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1963-1969 (Box 1)
  - Allied Nations Military Office, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1964-1968 (Box 1)
  - American Council on Education: High Ed. And National Affairs, 1964-1969 (Box 1)
  - Americans for Reappraisal of Far-East Policy (ARFEP), 1966 (Box 1)
  - Arts Festival, 1966-1969 (Box 1)
  - Arts Management, 1965-1969 (Box 1)
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU): funding of student government, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Association of College Unions (ACU): April 1967 conference, The College Union and Campus Store (#6) (Box 1)
  - ACU: April 1967 conference, Computers - a New Dimension in Management (#15) (Box 1)
  - ACU: April 1967 conference, Promotional Graphics (#24) (Box 1)
  - ACU: April 1967 conference, Recreational Facilities and Programs (#32) (Box 1)
  - ACU: April 1967 conference, Role of College Union Director on Small College Campus (#40) (Box 1)
  - ACU: April 1967 conference, miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - ACU: conference programs, 1960s (Box 2)
  - ACU: conferences, 1961-1966 (Box 2)
  - ACU: Programs Committee #1, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - ACU: Programs Committee #2, 1967 (Box 2)
  - ACU: correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 2)
  - Association of College and University Concert Managers, December 1967 Conference (Box 2)
  - Association of College and University Concert Managers (ACUM): correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 2)
  - ACUM: 1965 & 1966 conferences (Box 2)
  - ACUM: miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
  - ACUM: 1964 conference (Box 2)
  - ACUM: 1963 conference (Box 3)
  - Associated Council of the Arts: correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 3)
  - Associated Council of the Arts: conferences, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
  - Athletic Council, 1962-1966 (Box 3)
  - Baldwin Auditorium, 1965-1969 (Box 3)
  - Band & Orchestra, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
  - Baumgartner, Paul, pianist: correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
  - Blazers: correspondence, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Boy's Club of Durham, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Business Division Seminars, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Calendar: correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
  - Campus Club, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - Campus of Duke University: brochures, undated (Box 3)
  - Carillon: correspondence with Anton Brees, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Carillon: program bulletins (includes other institutions), undated (Box 3)
  - Carillon: correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
  - Carillon: general correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 3)
  - Carillon: general correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 3)
  - Chamber Music Series: correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 3)
  - Chapel: correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 3)
  - Chapel: Religious Activities: personnel, 1961-1965 (Box 4)
  - Chapel: Religious Activities, 1963-1969 (Box 4)
  - Chapel: Religious Conferences, 1964-1965 (Box 4)
  - Chapel: Rehabilitation Committee, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Chapel Choir Spring Oratorio: Estimated expense, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Choral Activities: Glee Clubs, 1961-1969 (Box 4)
  - Choral Activities: Glee Clubs' congratulatory letters, 1964-1967 (Box 4)
  - Choral Activities, 1961-1970 (Box 4)
  - Choral Activities: oratorio performances in the Duke Chapel, 1965-1967 (Box 4)
  - Coffee Hour (Celestial Omnibus), 1967-1969 (Box 4)
  - Colloquium In Loco Parentis, undated (Box 4)
  - Commandant's Trophy (USMC), 1965-1966 (Box 4)
  - Commencement: correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 4)
  - Commitment to Undergraduate Teaching, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Duke-North Carolina Central Joint Committee to examine areas of mutual concern, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Committee on Educational Administration, 1963-1969 (Box 4)
  - Conferences, 1965-1969; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Conferences, 1965-1969 (Box 5)
  - Conference: "The Campus Crisis", circa 1969 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence: general, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence: personal, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence: personal, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence: general, 1963-1965 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence: personal, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence: general, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence: general, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence: personal, 1963-1964 (Box 6)
  - Mayor's Council on Youth Opportunity, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Cultural Events, 1963-1969 (Box 6)
  - Curriculum: Non-Curricular credit proposal, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Cost Reduction Office (formerly Special Project office), 1969 (Box 6)
  - Council on Leaders & Specialists, 1966-1969 (Box 6)
  - Counseling Center, 1964-1967 (Box 6)
  - Community Shelter Plan, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1963-1969 (Box 6)
  - Debate Activities, 1963-1970 (Box 6)
  - Department Chairman, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Dining Halls: correspondence re:, 1965-1968 (Box 6)
  - Directory (faculty), 1968 (Box 6)
  - Directory (students), 1964-1968 (Box 6)
  - Duke Players, 1962-1970 (Box 7)
  - Duke Players, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Duke Players: applicants, 1969-1969 (Box 7)
  - Duke Players: director applicants, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Duke Players: personnel, 1966-1970 (Box 7)
  - Duke Players: budget material, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Duke Players: financial summary & suggestions, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Duke Forum, 1967 (Box 7)
  - Durham Community Planning Council, 1965-1967 (Box 7)
  - Durham Community Planning Council: Cultural Survey, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - Durham County Society for Crippled Children & Adults, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Durham County Society for Crippled Children & Adults: financial, 1962-1969 (Box 7)
  - Durham County Society for Crippled Children & Adults, 1961-1970 (Box 8)
  - Durham Liberal Alliance: newsletter, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Durham Civic & Cultural Center Commission, 1964-1969 (Box 8)
  - Durham Civic & Cultural Center Commission: Macfayden & Knowler Architects, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Durham Civic & Cultural Center Commission: Booz, Allen & Hamilton, Inc. (management consultants), 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Durham Civic & Cultural Center Commission: William Briggs (consultant), 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Durham Civic & Cultural Center Commission: Raymond Loewy/William Snaith, inc., 1966-1969 (Box 8)
  - Durham Civic & Cultural Center Commission: Requirements Subcommittee, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Durham Committee on Community Relations, 1964-1965 (Box 8)
  - Duke University: transfer journal voucher, 1970 (Box 8)
  - ECOS of Durham & Duke (environmental organizations), 1970 (Box 8)
  - Educational Administration Advisory Group, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Educational Facilities Committee: floor plans for Union & Flowers, undated (Box 8)
  - Educational Facilities Committee: the Round Board, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Educational Facilities Committee: The Arts Center, 1963-1966 (Box 9)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1966 March (Box 9)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories Project, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1965 (Box 9)
  - Emergency Care, 1964-1969 (Box 9)
  - Erdahl Fund, 1960-1964 (Box 9)
  - Faculty Club, 1963-1968 (Box 9)
  - Faculty & Staff, 1970 (Box 9)
  - financial aid: correspondence re:, 1965-1968 (Box 9)
  - football ushers, 1967 (Box 9)
  - football: miscellaneous correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
  - ford foundation study, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
  - foreign visitors, A-L, 1963-1966 (Box 9)
  - foreign visitors, M-Z, 1963-1966 (Box 9)
  - foreign visitors: Shibayama Roshi, 1964-1968 (Box 10)
  - foreign students office, 1964-1966 (Box 10)
  - fraternities: Beta Theta Pi correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 10)
  - fraternities: correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 10)
  - fraternities: Beta Theta Pi financial reports, 1963-1968 (Box 10)
  - free academic senate, 1969 (Box 10)
  - freshmen: general, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
  - freshman week, 1964-1968 (Box 10)
  - Friday Luncheon Group, 1964-1969 (Box 10)
  - Fund for Experimental Education, 1967-1969 (Box 10)
  - Game Room, 1965-1969 (Box 10)
  - Graduate Student Association, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Gray, Richard (Drama), 1966-1968 (Box 10)
  - Department of Health & Physical Education, 1966-1970 (Box 10)
  - Heart Fund: correspondence, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Highway Engineers Study team from Brazil, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Honors Programs, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Honors System, 1963-1969 (Box 11)
  - Hoof & Horn, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Department of Housing, 1965-1970 (Box 11)
  - Housing: Damar Study, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Housing: Town House Apartments, 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - Housing: West Campus, 1963-1969 (Box 11)
  - Housing Woman's College, 1963-1969 (Box 11)
  - Housing Graduate Center, 1964-1970 (Box 11)
  - Housing Graduate Center, 1964-1970 (Box 188)
    Conditions Governing Access
    FERPA restricted until 2040.
  - Housing: Hanes Annex, 1965-1970 (Box 11)
  - Housing: Alternative Living Arrangements (MSGA Dorm Evaluation Commission), 1970 (Box 11)
  - Housing: MSGA & IFC joint proposal, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Housing: Association of Independent Houses, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Inaugural Committee, 1963-1970 (Box 11)
  - Integration, 1964-1966 (Box 11)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Intramural meetings, 1968-1970 (Box 11)
  - Intramural program, 1964-1970 (Box 11)
  - Information Desk, 1966-1970 (Box 11)
  - Office of Information Services, 1965-1970 (Box 12)
  - The Institutional System (ESSO) project, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Intergovernmental Council, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - International (Studies) Office, 1965-1970 (Box 12)
  - Duke Indoor Stadium, 1965-1970 (Box 12)
  - Infirmary: annual report, 1964-1965 (Box 12)
  - Invitations, 1963-1970 (Box 12)
  - Joint Reunion (for 1950, '51, '52 classes), 1971 (Box 12)
  - Key Card System, 1970 (Box 12)
  - Lectures, 1954-1967 (Box 12)
  - Legislature Minutes, undated (Box 12)
  - Liberal Action Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 12)
  - Library, 1964-1969 (Box 12)
  - Loyalty Fund, 1965-1970 (Box 12)
  - Medical School: Program Cost Study, 1959-1960 (Box 12)
  - Men's Student Government Association (MSGA): correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 12)
  - MSGA: constitution (revisions), undated (Box 12)
  - MSGA: Drinking regulations report, 1961 (Box 12)
  - MSGA - housing conditions questionnaire, undated (Box 12)
  - MSGA: laws, undated (Box 12)
  - MSGA: Leadership program, undated (Box 12)
  - MSGA: minutes of Senate meetings, 1961-1967 (Box 12)
  - MSGA: parking regulations, undated (Box 12)
  - MSGA: speakers, Stokely Carmichael & Arnold Johnson, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - MSGA: student involvement in extra-campus affairs, undated (Box 12)
  - Memberships policy (professional organizations), 1969 (Box 12)
  - Methodist Youth Fellowship, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Methodist Student Center, 1967 (Box 12)
  - MOBE/Duke Moratorium, 1969 (Box 12)
  - "Sing Out '66", 1966 (Box 13)
  - Music miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 13)
  - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators (NASPA), 1970 (Box 13)
  - National Leadership Methods, 1970 (Box 13)
  - United States National Students Associations (NSA), 1968 (Box 13)
  - National Training Laboratories, 1964-1967 (Box 13)
  - Richard Nickolas, American Choreographic Co., 1967 (Box 13)
  - North Carolina Fund, 1968 (Box 13)
  - Nursing Student Government Association, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
  - Office of Cultural Affairs, 1969 (Box 13)
  - Office of Cultural Affairs: Artist's Series, 1969-1970 (Box 13)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa (ODK): Spring 1969 Initiates (Box 13)
  - Office of Institutional Advancement, 1961-1969 (Box 13)
  - Office of Institutional Advancement: Fifth Decade Campaign summary reports, undated (Box 13)
  - Office of Institutional Studies: Summer Activities of Students survey, 1961-1965 (Box 13)
  - Office of Placement Series (formerly Appointment Office), 1969 (Box 13)
  - Ombudsman & Rumor Control Board, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, circa 1936-1950 (Box 14)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1960-1966 (Box 14)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa (ODK), 1963-1968 (Box 14)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa: rosters, 1927-1949 (Box 14)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, Rho Circle: minutes, 1964-1967 (Box 14)
  - Order of Hippocrates, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Organ: general, 1964-1969 (Box 14)
  - Page Auditorium, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - Pan-Hellenic Council, 1965-1966 (Box 14)
  - Peace Corps: Campus Committee, 1962-1966 (Box 14)
  - Peace Corps: correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 14)
  - Peace Corps: Duke Students Participating, 1962-1966 (Box 15)
  - Peace Corps: Purdue University report, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Peace Corps: testing, 1965-1967 (Box 15)
  - Peace Corps week, 1964-1966 (Box 15)
  - Personal Adjustment & Human Relations, Committee on, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Personnel: general, 1966-1970 (Box 15)
  - Personnel: job opportunities, non-Duke, 1965-1968 (Box 15)
  - Personnel: National Association of Student Personnel Administrators, 1962-1969 (Box 15)
  - Personnel: Non-academic employees associations, 1968-1970 (Box 15)
  - Personnel: Police Officer Training, 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Personnel: student, undated (Box 15)
  - Personnel: Union Local 77, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Duke University Penal Code, undated (Box 15)
  - Pre-Medical Society, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Presidency: announcement of Dr. Knight's acceptance, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 1969 (Box 15)
  - The Print Shop, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Housing: Preliminary Report of Demand in Decade Ahead, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Place of the Colleges in the University, report, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Program Management department, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Project of the Americas, 1966-1967 (Box 15)
  - Project Bolivia, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Project Outreach, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Provost Group: minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 16)
  - Psychology Department, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Publications Board: 1970 questionnaire (Box 16)
  - Radio Council, 1964-1968 (Box 16)
  - Radio Station: FM committee, 1962-1968 (Box 16)
  - Radio Station: WDBS correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 16)
  - Radio Station: WDBS report, 1964-1967 (Box 16)
  - Randolph-Macon College, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Recreation Committee of the University Community, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Regulations Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 16)
  - Report: Committee on Physical Education, 1961-1962 (Box 16)
  - Report: Emory University "Self-Study", undated (Box 16)
  - Report: The Culture of the University: Governance & Education (UC Berkeley Study 1968) (Box 16)
  - Report: Indiana University (topic: African Americans in higher education), 1968 (Box 17)
  - Report: Sindler Commission report, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Report: Duke University: Educational Perspectives & Vistas, 1965 (Box 17)
  - Report: Byrne report re: Reorganization of the University of California, 1965 (Box 17)
  - Report to the President, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - Report to the President, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Report to the President, 1964 May (Box 17)
  - Report to the President, 1964-1968 (Box 17)
  - Report to the President, 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - Report to the President, 1961-1962 (Box 17)
  - Report to the President, 1961-1963 (Box 17)
  - Report to the President, 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Report to the Board of Trustees, 1962 November (Box 17)
  - Report to the Board of Trustees, 1963 June (Box 17)
  - Report to the Board of Trustees, 1968 June (Box 17)
  - Report: "Reforming General Education," Daniel Bell, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Report: Renovations - Construction for Duke University: Past, Present, & Future, 1964 (Box 17)
  - Report: Vanderbilt University Parietals Subcommittee, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Resident Advisor Program: Syracuse University, 1963 (Box 18)
  - ROTC (AF & N), 1965 (Box 18)
  - Rugby Football Club: expenses, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Sailing Club, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - Scheduling Committee, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Scholarships: correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18)
  - School of Engineering, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
  - School of Nursing, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - School to College: Opportunities for Postsecondary Education (SCOPE), 1967 (Box 18)
  - Henry Schuman Music Prize, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Security, 1965-1968 (Box 18)
  - William Senhauser Memorial Prize, 1956-1968 (Box 18)
  - Soccer Club, 1967-1967 (Box 18)
  - Southern Association of Colleges & Schools (SACS) visit, 1965 October 10 (Box 18)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (SSOC), 1968-1968 (Box 18)
  - Student Perspective, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Student "Philosophy", 1964 (Box 18)
  - Student Records, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
    About the handling of student records in general, as policy; does not contain records of students.
  - Student Union: Arts Festival Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 18)
  - Student Union: Board of Governors, 1964-1968 (Box 18)
  - Student Union: budgets, 1964-1968 (Box 18)
  - Student Union: Constitution drafts, 1964-1965 (Box 18)
  - Student Union: general, 1959-1968 (Box 18)
  - Student Union: Union miscellaneous (other institutions), undated (Box 19)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1966-1969 (Box 19)
  - Summer Session office, 1967-1969 (Box 19)
  - Summer Study Abroad program, undated (Box 19)
  - Supervisory Committee for the Faculty Advisory System, 1965 (Box 19)
  - The Supremes 1966 Concert (Box 19)
  - Suspension penalty (attendance regulations), 1964 (Box 19)
  - Symposiums, 1962-1968 (Box 19)
  - Tax exemptions, 1961-1965 (Box 19)
  - Telegrams, undated (Box 19)
  - Telephones, 1963-1969 (Box 19)
  - Television, 1964-1965 (Box 19)
  - TIAA CREF, 1965-1968 (Box 19)
  - Ticket Sales: instructions, 1965-1966 (Box 19)
  - Joseph H. Tieger, 1964-1967 (Box 188)
    FERPA restricted until 2037.
  - Tours, 1964-1967 (Box 19)
  - Track & Field officials, 1970 (Box 19)
  - Trinity College, 1964-1968 (Box 19)
  - Troika, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Trustee-Administration Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Trustee-Student Liaison Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Trustees of Duke University, 1965-1968 (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: correspondence, 1967 (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: Curriculum Committee, 1961-1969 (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: lists of committees, 1961-1966 (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: member lists, 1961-1969 (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: Religion requirement, undated (Box 19)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council: Summary of Actions & Minutes, 1961-1969 (Box 20)